(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(本剧与特定人物 机构 团体 案件无关 纯属虚构 特此告知)
(Episode 5) Alas, let’s fight each other
(第5集) 唉唷 我们斗学
(Lishui, early 1960s) Are you starving?
(1960年代初期 丽水) 饿坏了吧
Okay...Mom, let's feed you milk
好了…妈妈喂你喝奶吧
I'm going to weed the master's field
我要去老爷的田里除草
After you sow the seeds, go back first.
你播种完就先回去吧
Oh my god
天啊
Do I have to sow all that barley alone?
那些大麦全都要我一个人播种吗
I still have to take care of the kids
我还要照顾孩子耶
This is too much, right?
这未免也太过分了吧
We are not servants of the Joseon Dynasty
我们又不是朝鲜时代的仆人
Could it be that after you die? Will that master help you erect a monument to praise your virtues?
难道你死了以后 那个老爷会帮你立个颂德碑吗
Really, what do you know?
真是的 你懂什么
I know everything, okay?
我什么都懂好吗
If you know everything, don't say such things
什么都懂就不要说这种话
It’s not that I’m ungrateful
我又不是不懂得感恩
I just think you paid too much
我只是觉得你付出得太超过了
One person takes care of that family's farm work That's not enough
一个人包办那户人家的农活 那样还不够
Even our crops Give it to them after the harvest
连我们家的农作物 收成后都给他们
Other long-term workers will not do their job to the death.
其他的长工也不会做得要死要活
You're the only one who has lost your mind
就你一个人死脑筋
That's what I mean
我是这个意思
Even if others don't do it I have to do this too
就算别人不这么做 我也得这样做
It’s those people who don’t know how to be grateful
是那群人不懂得感恩
Even if the world is in decline
就算世风日下
We must not forget the principles of life
我们也不能忘记做人的道理
Sigh, if only everyone were like you
唉唷 要是大家都像你一样
The world no longer needs Confucius and Mencius.
这世界就不需要孔子和孟子了啦
That old woman is really... You're leaving soon...
那个老太婆 真是的… 你快走啦…
Don't worry about my life or death. Just leave.
不用管我的死活 你快走
Practice more principles of being a human being.
多多实践做人的道理吧
By the way, I seem to be pregnant again
对了 我好像又怀孕了
My period has not come for three months
我的月经已经三个月没来了
You burn the grass
你把草烧一烧
Leave the rest of the sowing work to me
剩下的播种作业交给我
You go back and rest
你回去休息吧
Alas, Douxue
唉唷 斗学
I heard you are going to have a brother
听到你要有个弟弟了
Your dad still looks indifferent
你爸还是一副漠不关心的样子
You will definitely not be like your dad when you grow up.
你长大绝对不能像你爸那样喔
You are really a person. Please ride slower.
你这个人真是的 骑慢一点啦
If you ride like this, I will go to see King Yama first.
你这样骑 我会先去见阎罗王啦
Oh my god
天啊
The master must be killed quickly Just send it to a big hospital in Gwangju
必须赶快把老爷 送到光州的大医院去才行
Can we call an ambulance now?
现在能叫救护车吗
Okay, let me make a call
可以 让我打个电话
No need…
不用了…
Dad
爸
Send the doctor home
送医生回家
Call Douxue's father to come in
叫斗学的爸爸进来
Master
老爷
I don't have to ask you to make him your adopted son.
我不是非得要你让他当养子
But if the second child is a son Just do it
但倘若老二是个儿子的话 就那么做吧
Because my wife cannot give birth to a child...
因为我的媳妇生不出孩子…
My sins are heavy
我的罪孽深重
It doesn’t matter if there are no descendants to offer sacrifices after death...
死后没有子孙祭祀也没关系…
But I'm afraid I won't have the face to see my ancestors after I die
但我怕死后没有脸见列祖列宗
I'll take care of you
算我拜托你了
Master
老爷
Even so
即便如此
We are of untouchable blood...
我们这种贱民的血脉…
Young-sik
英植
Big brother
大哥
Please
拜托你了
I have only one request
我只有一个要求
Since we have to do this
既然要这么做
Just treat that child as my own.
那个孩子就当作是我亲生的吧
I know
我知道了
I will keep this matter secret
这件事我会保密
I will keep it in my heart until I die
到死为止 我都会放在心里
Master
老爷
thank you
谢谢你
Why are you crying like this
你怎么哭成这样
Because it's sad...
因为难过啊…
The child is not born yet
孩子都还没出生
He was snatched away as an adopted son Is this true?
就被人家抢走当作养子 这像话吗
If he is a son, he will be adopted by them
如果是儿子才会给他们当养子
And how do you say someone snatched it away?
而且你怎么说是人家抢走的呢
On the contrary, we are receiving favors from others, right?
反倒是我们受人恩惠吧
Oh my god, the kids are going to be taken away.
天啊 孩子都要被抢走了
What kind of favor is this?
这算哪门子的恩惠
Think about it
你想想看
Every spring famine period It’s too hard to eat with one more mouth
每到春荒时期 多一张嘴吃饭都嫌辛苦了
People are willing to help raise children What a lot to be thankful for
人家愿意帮忙养小孩 是多值得感恩的事
Say it again
再说
our children To grow up well in such a wealthy family
我们的孩子 能在那么富有的人家好好长大
How gratifying it would be for us to see
我们看了该有多欣慰
But will that kid recognize us?
但那个孩子会认得我们吗
You are a real person Does it matter whether he recognizes us or not?
你这个人真是的 他认不认得我们 有什么重要
we know it ourselves As long as God knows and Earth knows, that’s fine
我们自己知道 还有天知地知就好啦
I can't hold him in my arms Can you still say it’s your own child?
没办法抱在怀中 还能说是自己的孩子吗
The child will think that those who raise him are his parents
孩子会认为养他的人才是父母
Even if he grows up to be a judge or a prosecutor It's of no use at all
就算他长大当法官 当检察官 也一点用也没有
If... is a son
如果…是个儿子
Just consider him lucky.
就当作是他有福气吧
Why did I break up with you?
为什么我跟你分手之后
She got married in a hurry and became a woman.
就匆忙地嫁做人妇了呢
Guro Industrial Zone happened again What about the headache?
九老工业区又发生了 让人头痛的事呢
I will do it the same way as last time
我会比照上次的方式办理
Don't be too arrogant. Just follow your brother's lead.
你不要太嚣张 好好跟着大哥做
Otherwise, you can just hide in the corner
不然你就躲在角落也行
(Fangri Industrial)
(方日实业)
(Demand to stop suppressing trade unions)
(要求停止对工会的打压)
thank you
谢谢您
Douxue Yes eldest brother
斗学 是 大哥
Yongbi
永弼
(Personal profile Wen Dongxiu)
(个人档案 文东秀)
This guy is the culprit
这个家伙是罪魁祸首
Dropped out of a prestigious university
从名门大学中辍
Pretending to be employed in a factory
假装到工厂里就业
Inciting workers who know nothing
煽动什么都不懂的工人
bring down the company
把公司搞垮
(Unite and fight) This despicable man
(团结 抗争) 这个卑鄙小人
It must be in the factory
一定就在工厂里面
We must catch him, you know?
绝对要抓到他 知道了吧
Brother, I also came to work in a factory in Seoul.
哥 我也来首尔的工厂上班了
Bangil Industrial Co., Ltd. just over Guro-ri
就在九老里那边的方日实业
They make hinges and razors.
是做铰链跟刮胡刀的
Then just ask the police to arrest them.
那叫警察把他们抓走就好了吧
After the union was established here
这里的工会成立后
The company has been closed down
公司就办理停业了
So there is no reason to arrest workers
所以没有理由能逮捕工人
But we still have to get rid of that kid.
但还是要把那个小子给除掉才行
See what I mean
明白我的意思吧
I understand
我懂了
Do you understand?
你们听懂了吧
Yes brother
是的 大哥
follow me
跟我来
Wait to die
等着受死吧
Brat
臭小子
Brother, are you okay?
大哥 你没事吧
Damn...
可恶…
Come with us obediently
乖乖跟我们走吧
Brother
哥
Brother, please don’t do this
哥 拜托你别这样
Don't do this
不要这样
Wen Dongxiu
文东秀
Brat
臭小子
Let's go
走啦
Brother, don't be like this
哥 不要这样
(Requesting to revoke the temporary suspension of business and protect the right to survival)
(要求撤销假停业 保障生存权)
(Trustworthy Seoul Police)
(值得信赖的首尔警察)
Teacher…
老师…
Zhenyu…
贞玉…
let go
放手
Take me away too
也把我带走吧
I asked you to take me away
我叫你把我带走啊
Be calm
你安分点
let go
放手
Hello
喂
come with us
跟我们走吧
Take care of your family
管好你的家人吧
Give this to Boss Lian
把这个交给廉老板
I finally got you out
我好不容易才把你弄出来的
Just stay at home
你就乖乖待在家里
I'm really grateful
还真是感激不尽
If I didn't have a gangster brother...
要不是我有个流氓哥哥…
Hello
喂
do you know what you are doing
你知道自己在做什么吗
Those black-hearted bosses are worse than animals
那些黑心的老板禽兽不如
And you are acting as their lackey
而你却在当他们的走狗
where are you going
你要去哪里
Let go, I want to be with my friends
放手 我要跟我的伙伴们在一起
your partner?
你的伙伴吗
Those who go to night school Are you a partner in the demonstration?
那些去上夜校 参加示威的伙伴吗
Are those guys more important than family?
那些家伙比家人还重要吗
They are my family and my comrades
他们就是我的家人 是我的同志
Gay?
同志吗
It seems you have become a red element too, right?
看来你也变成赤色分子了吧
If you go to the police station now
你现在要是去警察局
You might be arrested and sent to jail directly.
可能会直接被抓去坐牢
If you want me to go to jail, I will sit there.
要我坐牢我就坐啊
Only criminals like you are afraid of going to jail
像你这种犯罪者才会害怕坐牢
I'm not afraid at all
我一点都不怕
why
为什么
Because all I do is In order to live with dignity
因为我做这些都只是 为了活得有尊严一点
Abominable
可恶
Why on earth do you have to live like this?
你到底为什么要过这种日子
You were obviously not this kind of person before
你以前明明不是这种人
Don’t you feel that you are ashamed of God?
你都不觉得自己愧对上天吗
After all, I'm used to living a life without seeing the light of day.
毕竟不见天日的生活我过惯了
What's more
更何况
God won't care about a guy like me.
上天也不会管我这种家伙的
Zhenyu
贞玉
Douxue
斗学
OMG…
天啊…
You...look at your virtues
你…看看你这副德行
Go back
回去吧
It's best not to let your parents know about this
这件事最好别让爸妈知道
what does this mean
这是什么意思
What can't we know?
什么事不能让我们知道
Mom, don’t let Zhenyu go out
妈 不要让贞玉外出
Just let her stay home
让她待在家就好
Don't let her go to work in the company
不要让她去公司上班
Company?
公司吗
The factory is temporarily closed
工厂暂时关门了
So let her eat and sleep at home, okay?
所以就让她在家吃好睡好吧
Did you get into trouble?
你闯祸了吗
The person who caused trouble is my brother
闯祸的人是哥哥
The son who made you proud
曾让你们自豪的儿子
Now he's gone to be a gangster.
现在跑去当黑道流氓了
What is she talking about?
她在说什么啊
Mom
妈
Don't let Zhenyu go to work in the factory anymore
你别再让贞玉去工厂上班了
Let her go to college
让她去读大学
I will be responsible for her tuition
我会负责她的学费
I came here to give you this
我是要给你这个才来的
This…
这个…
Take it back
你拿回去吧
I asked you to take it back
我叫你拿回去
My son was bought with us in mind. why are you like this
儿子是为我们着想才买来的 你干嘛这样
What have you been doing lately?
你最近到底都在做什么
Zhenyu just said it
刚刚贞玉说过啦
I'm being a gangster
我在当流氓
You bastard
你这个混帐小子
The arrogant dad...
斗学的爸…
What's wrong
怎么了
You beat me like you did before
你就像以前那样揍我啊
It's all because of my dad that I'm like this.
我会变成这样 都是爸害的
Douxue
斗学
Dou Xue Even so You shouldn't live like this either
斗学 即便如此 你也不该这样过日子
How can you be a gangster?
你怎么可以去当流氓
You are obviously a kind child
你明明就是个善良的孩子
Mom, you don’t understand
妈 你不懂啦
I don't understand where...
我哪里不懂了…
An ex-con with nothing and no skills.
一无所有 不学无术的前科犯
What else can you do after you get out of prison?
出狱后还能做什么
Do you want me to go back to my hometown to farm?
要我回老家种田吗
Do you have fields that I can plant?
你们有田能让我种吗
Dad, what can you say?
爸 你倒是说点什么啊
I've always listened to you
我一直以来都很听你的话
If you tell me not to study, I will give up studying.
你叫我别念书 我就放弃念书
If you tell me to go to jail, I will go to jail.
你叫我去坐牢 我就去坐牢
After I get out of prison
等我出狱之后
All you can do is be a gangster.
能做的事就只有当流氓啊
If you don't even let me do this
要是连这都不让我做
How about I just die?
我干脆去死一死怎么样
You answer me
你回答我啊
Douxue…
斗学…
I'm definitely not my father's son
我一定不是爸的儿子
(Supreme Prosecutor's Office)
(最高检察署)
This is the Supreme Prosecutor's Office
这里是最高检察署
All trainees, please follow me
请各位研修生跟我来
Yes, he is Choi Cheol-woong
对啊 他就是崔哲雄
The guy who was the mole before
之前当内鬼的那个家伙
Let's go upstairs
我们上楼吧
congratulations
恭喜你
long time no see
好久不见
why are you here
你为什么会在这里
Why else
还能为什么
I work here too
我也在这里工作啊
to you
给你
(Wu Wanxu)
(吴万旭)
The Ministry of Security and Enterprise sent me to work here.
是安企部派我到这里工作的
I believe…
我相信…
Will you help me as much as you did before?
你会像以前那样大力帮忙我吧
Let's have a cup of soju together later
我们之后再一起喝杯烧酒吧
Don't get me wrong
你别误会了
I'm no longer the puppet I used to be
我已经不是以前的那个傀儡了
I am Choi Cheol-woong, a prosecutor of the Republic of Korea.
我是大韩民国的检察官崔哲雄
Why are you like this? You are still just a trainee now, right?
你怎么这样呢 你现在还只是研修生吧
If you mess with me again
你要是再惹我一次
Don't blame me for tearing you into pieces
就别怪我把你碎尸万段
Do you want to be a prosecutor?
你想成为检察官吗
What can we do?
这可怎么办呢
The future prosecutor
未来的检察官大人
In the files of our Security and Enterprise Department I have your record
我们安企部的档案里 有你的纪录耶
I want you to serve the country
我为了让你替国家效忠
And let you retire early
还让你提早退伍
But you are completely uncooperative...
但你完全不配合…
But it doesn't matter
不过没关系啦
Is it possible to make more money as a lawyer anyway?
反正当律师可以赚更多钱嘛
Are you threatening me now?
你现在是在威胁我吗
How dare I
我怎么敢呢
I'm just reminding you that this is the reality
我只是提醒你现实就是如此
Results are important
成绩固然重要
But political orientation is also a part that must be considered
但政治倾向也是必须考量的部分
But you want to be a prosecutor It's not like there's no other way
不过你想当检察官 也不是没有办法啦
The prosecution currently lacks information on the All-Students Federation
检方目前还缺少全学联的情报
Because we didn’t provide everything to them
因为我们没有全提供给他们
I'm here today to give them relevant files
我今天是来给他们相关档案的
That's all information you already know
那些都是你已经知道的情报
As long as you report it personally on my behalf
只要你代替我亲自报告
There shouldn't be anyone I doubt your political leanings
应该就不会有任何人 怀疑你的政治倾向了
you now...
你现在…
Could it be...
该不会…
Do you want me to betray my friends with my own hands again?
又要我亲手出卖我的朋友吗
That's what you mean, right?
你就是这个意思 对吧
you didn't betray anyone
你并没有出卖任何人
Because whoever among us reports
因为我们之中 无论谁去报告
The result will be the same
结果都会一样
But if you do it instead of me
只是 如果由你代替我做这件事
you can achieve your goal
你就能达成你的目标
That being the case
既然如此
Just report it yourself
你自己去报告就好了
Why do you keep looking for me?
为什么老是要找上我
I'm not sure either
我也不太清楚呢
You half-assed dead mole
你这个半吊子的死内鬼
listen up
听好了
This is your last trial and chance
这是你最后的试炼和机会
Don't be a scumbag Always in the gray area
不要当个卑鄙小人 总是待在灰色地带
state your position
表明你的立场
See if you want to be a family with us
看你是要和我们当一家人
Or are we enemies?
还是与我们为敌
to be honest
老实说
I don't want to at all Reuse your waste
我一点都不想 把你这个废物再利用
I really can't understand Why are my parents so nice to you?
我真的无法理解 我家长官为什么对你这么好
If you see him someday
哪天你要是见到他
You must bow three thousand times to him
一定要向他行三千拜大礼
I'm waiting for you in front of the big conference room
我在大会议室前等你
If you don't show up within five minutes
要是五分钟内没出现的话
I'll just assume you don't want to be a family with us anymore
我就当你不想和我们做一家人了
In addition to Mingxingye and Hanjiang Film and Television Outside the theaters of these two film companies
除了明星兴业和汉江影配 这两间电影公司的戏院以外
All theaters on a pro-rata basis They were all eaten by the middle of us
所有比例拆帐制的戏院 都被我们中部吃下来了
But won’t we lose money by doing this?
但这么做我们不会亏损吗
If you look at each theater separately Theaters that are indeed losing money
如果将每间戏院分开来看 确实有亏损的戏院
But overall
但是整体而言
Because there are so many theaters We will never lose money
因为戏院数量很多 我们绝对不会亏损
You girl, you are very ambitious.
你这丫头 野心不小嘛
But if you expand your business too quickly
但要是你把事业规模扩张得太快
I'm afraid there won't be enough silver bullets
我怕银弹会不够
Eating too fast will break the bowl
吃得太快会弄破碗
let's take our time
我们慢慢来吧
I know your hard work
我知道您的辛苦之处
But please hold on a little longer
但请您再撑一下吧
Bring something
东西拿来
Wow, this is really enviable
唉唷 还真让人羡慕呢
Gao Standing Committee
高常务
If your ability to do things is the same as Dingchen I can also go through fire and water for you
要是你的办事能力跟定辰一样 我也能为你赴汤蹈火
what is this
这是什么
Certificate of ownership of Nanhai Theater
南海戏院的所有权状
what
什么
(Certificate of ownership Nanhai Cinema)
(所有权状 南海戏院)
boss
老板
Your aunt sold the Nanhai Theater
你姑姑把南海戏院卖掉了
I spent a lot of effort Just got it back
我可是费了好大一番功夫 才把它给找回来的
Thank you very much
真的太感谢您了
Our boss Gao is the best
我们的高老板最棒了
Oh, it's true
唉唷 真是的
I envy you so much
我好羡慕你
It's really disgusting
真是的 肉麻死了
(Namdo Film Company Seoul Office)
(南道电影公司 首尔办事处)
Boss, thank you very much
老板 真的很谢谢您
I'll contact you again
我再跟您联络
let's go
我们走吧
this gives you
这给您
I'm so sorry to trouble you every time.
每次都麻烦您 真是不好意思
Don't say that. To me it's an investment.
别这么说 对我而言这是投资
I am also very happy to see the company grow
看到公司壮大 我也很开心
Please confirm it
您确认一下吧
Boss Jin, thank you
金老板 谢谢你
The same thing happened with Nanhai Theater
南海戏院的事也是
Our little girl is so happy
我们的小丫头超开心呢
As long as she's happy
她开心就好
The core of the All-Students Federation
全学联的核心
(Organization Chart of the All-Students Federation) It's the Three People's Struggle Committee
(全学联组织图) 是三民斗争委员会
Three People's Struggle Committee?
三民斗争委员会吗
The Committee of the Three People's Struggles promotes The driving force and vanguard force behind the All-Students Federation
三民斗争委员会是促进 全学联的幕后推手和先锋部队
Their line is more radical
他们的路线更激进
future…
未来…
There is a high possibility of sudden violent demonstrations
很有可能进行突袭式暴力示威
Therefore, compared with the headquarters of the All-Students Federation,
因此比起全学联的指挥部
Three People's Struggle Committee Headquarters
三民斗争委员会指挥部的
Kwon Dong-hwi Choi Chang-won Park Deok-yeon…
权东辉 崔常元 朴得延…
Cui Zhexiong
崔哲雄
Don't live in such a shameful way
不要活得那么丢人现眼吧
If I really am a mole
如果我真的是内鬼
Whether it's brother or someone else
无论是哥 还是其他人
None of them will be here now
现在全都不会在这里了
(Arrest the headquarters of the Three People's Struggle Committee...)
(逮捕三民斗争委员会指挥部…)
(Arrest of the Three People's Struggle Committee Headquarters is the first priority)
(逮捕三民斗争委员会指挥部 是首要之务)
what is he doing...
他在做什么…
Damn...
可恶…
sorry
抱歉
Don't be nervous
不要紧张
Young people who contribute to the country
为国家贡献的年轻人
Don't be discouraged
千万不能泄气
See you next time
我们下次见
If you become a red molecule This record cannot be washed away no matter how you wash it.
如果成为赤色分子 这个纪录是怎么洗也洗不掉的
I really don’t know how your sister could do this Get involved with them
真不知道你妹怎么会 跟他们扯上关系
My friend's sister works in a textile factory
我朋友的妹妹在纺织工厂上班
according to her There are no red molecules in it at all
根据她的说法 里面根本没有赤色分子
Because the boss treats them really badly
因为老板对他们真的很恶劣
Most people are protesting against the boss Just joined the demonstration
大部分的人都是为了抗议老板 才加入示威
I want to fight my brother’s sister He should also be from that group.
我想斗学哥的妹妹 应该也是那一派的人
Brother, don't worry too much
大哥 您就别太担心了
What do you know? How dare you talk nonsense?
你懂什么啊 还敢胡说八道
A guy who didn't even graduate from junior high school
连国中都没毕业的家伙
Why are you suddenly talking about academic qualifications?
干嘛突然扯到学历啊
Is it because I don’t want to study that I can’t graduate?
难道是我不想读书才毕不了业吗
How many times have I told you It’s because my family doesn’t have money to pay tuition fees
我跟你说过多少次 是因为家里没钱缴学费
I gave the opportunity to study to my younger brothers and sisters
我把读书的机会让给了弟弟妹妹
Then why don't you take the entrance exam while you're in prison?
那你在监狱里干嘛不考入学考试
You don’t have to pay tuition for taking exams
考试又不用缴学费
There is no atmosphere for reading in prison
监狱里又没有读书的气氛
I need someone to study with me It makes me excited to read it
要有人跟我一起读书 读起来才起劲啊
It's full of thieves and fraudsters There are also a bunch of pretty boys
里面都是小偷 诈欺犯 还有一堆小白脸
How can I continue reading, you brat?
我哪还读得下去 臭小子
Really bad boy
真是的 臭小子
Is it because there are classmates who study together?
难道斗学是因为有同学一起读书
Did you just pass the entrance exam?
才通过了入学考试吗
What nonsense are you talking about?
说什么狗屁倒灶的话
Damn it, don't hit me
可恶 不要打我啦
Really
真是的
Big brother is here...
大哥来了…
You are here
你来啦
How are they going?
怎么样 他们进行得如何了
It seems that Yongpil has finally taken action.
永弼好像终于开始行动了
Yongbi?
永弼吗
Later than I expected
比我预计的还晚呢
When will they probably take action?
他们大概什么时候会出手
Yongbi will handle it with you. After the incident at Guro Industrial Zone
永弼跟你一起处理完 九老工业区的事之后
So I went to see Mr. Park from the United Wine Dealers.
就去见了联合酒商的朴常务
It seems that Mr. Park is trying to frame you. All transaction information is ready
朴常务好像把要栽赃给你的 交易资料都做好了
I think they should be there within a week
我认为他们应该一周内就会出手
great
太好了
Start protecting aggressive learning today
今天开始要保护好斗学
Yong Pil may launch a surprise attack at any time
永弼随时都有可能会进行突袭
Yes brother
是的 大哥
I know
我知道了
The guy who wants to treat me to delicious food tonight
晚上要请我吃好料的家伙
Why did you have to call me here at noon?
干嘛非得中午就把我叫来这里
What is this?
这算什么嘛
Sorry, I'm so hungry
抱歉 我肚子太饿了
How about falling in love with me?
那个 跟我谈恋爱怎么样
what
什么
I asked you how the business deal went
我问你生意谈得怎么样了
Hello Cui Zhexiong
喂 崔哲雄
What do you want to say to me?
你到底想跟我说什么
do you want to be my boyfriend
你想当我男朋友吗
Right
对啊
how do you know
你怎么知道
You can read minds
你会读心术喔
Do you know what kind of morning makes me happiest?
你知道怎样的早晨最让我开心吗
It’s the morning I wake up after dreaming about you
是梦到你后醒来的早晨
Although I will feel a little empty when I wake up
虽然醒来后会有点空虚
But I feel really good
但是心情真的很好
Sorry, I made you confused
抱歉 我让你很不知所措吧
It seems like you're having a hard time, too.
看来你也过得很辛苦啊
I also had a very hard time
我也曾经过得超辛苦
See you like this now
看到你现在这样
Reminds me that I was in this state at that time
让我想起 我当时就是这个状态
The last time I met Douxue
上次我跟斗学见面时
His state is also very similar to yours.
他的状态也跟你很像呢
But I just scolded him
但我却只是痛骂了他一顿
You can't stand me
你无法招架我的
I will only make you suffer more
我只会让你更加痛苦
Let's just be good friends
我们就当好朋友吧
I'm leaving first
我先走了
Is this the only reason?
就只是这个理由吗
In addition to being unable to parry
除了无法招架之外
Is there no other reason that can convince me more?
没有其他更能说服我的理由吗
Could Brother Douxue be able to
难道斗学哥可以
Can't I?
我就不行吗
Let's make an appointment again some time
我们找时间再约吧
You must buy me a drink
一定要请我喝一杯喔
She hasn't eaten a bite
她一口也没吃呢
Here is the principal and interest
这里是本金和利息
We put a little more
我们有多放了一点
You don't have to be like this
您大可不必这样的
Thanks to you, the movie is a hit
托你的福 电影很卖座
Eating everything and wiping it clean is not the way to be a human being
吃干抹净可不是做人的道理
I am the dignified Cha Jinyu
我可是堂堂的车锦玉
I understand thank you
我知道了 谢谢您
However
不过
when do you plan to Introduce me to the president of the Overseas Chinese Association in Japan
你打算什么时候 介绍在日侨胞会长给我认识
I must say hello to him
我一定要跟他打声招呼才行
The president happens to be returning to Korea soon.
会长正好也快要回韩国了
I will convey it to you
我会帮您转达的
What?
什么啊
Aren’t you going to see Tetsuo today?
你今天不是要去见哲雄吗
Hey what's wrong with you
喂 你怎么了
What happened?
出了什么事吗
nothing
没什么
It's just that I'm too hopeless
只是我太没出息
Too bad
太坏了
who said that
是谁说的
who is
是谁
I'm going to tear his mouth apart
我要去撕烂他的嘴巴
Yoko
阳子啊
a person with a legitimate profession
一个有正当职业的人
and people without legitimate occupations
和没有正当职业的人
If you want to choose one of the two
要二选一的话
who would you choose
你会选谁
Of course they are people with legitimate professions
当然是有正当职业的人
right
对吧
But I keep thinking about that A person without a legitimate occupation
但我却一直想着那个 没有正当职业的人
That means you are not normal either
那代表你也不正常
You are crazy too
你也是疯子
right
对吧
Have you met Tetsuo?
你见到哲雄了吗
But...who is the person without a legitimate profession?
但是…没有正当职业的人是谁
who is
是谁
someone
某个人
some poor guy
某个可怜虫
Hey, listen carefully
喂 你听好了
It is fate to be with someone who has a legitimate profession
和有正当职业的人是缘分
It's a bad fate to be with someone who doesn't have it
和没有的人是孽缘
But
但是
People always misunderstand fate as fate
人们总会把孽缘误会成缘分
Then regret it again
然后再来后悔
Although I don’t know who that person is
虽然不知道那个人是谁
But please give up
但拜托你死心
Don't go to him
不要去找他
How can you drink without music?
喝酒怎么能少得了音乐
"You are a fool"
"你是傻瓜"
"Keeping him but speechless"
"留住他却说不出话"
"Keep him but can't say I love you"
"留住他却说不出我爱你"
"He will leave"
"他会离开"
"Tell him quickly"
"快告诉他"
"Every street that leaves no trace"
"每个没有留下痕迹的街道"
"Only people who are speechless"
"只有说不出话的人们"
"What's the use of giving your heart?"
"付出心意有什么用"
I hope there will be an entrance exam every month
希望每个月都能有入学考试
Do you want to be number one in the country? Do you have a big meal like this every month?
你想考全国第一 每个月这样吃大餐吗
No
不
Because I don’t have to see you through the bars
因为可以不用隔着铁窗见到你
"What's the use of hating"
"讨厌有什么用"
"You will definitely regret it after you leave"
"走了之后一定会后悔"
"Say quickly"
"快说"
It's because of you that I can persist until now
我是因为你才能坚持到现在
don't let go of my hand
不要放开我的手
"Say quickly"
"快说"
Who?
谁啊
wow
哇
The song is so nice
歌真好听
Miss Wu
吴小姐
who are you
你们是谁
Who sent you?
你们是谁派来的
(Boss Che Jinyu)
(车锦玉老板)
here
这里
it's me
是我
Auntie, something happened here
阿姨 这里出事了
Dingchen was kidnapped
定辰被人绑架了
what
什么
She was taken away by a group of hooligans
她被一群流氓带走了
Got it, I'll be there right away. Just wait.
知道了 我马上过去 你等等
Gao Standing Committee
高常务
Go and drive quickly
快去开车
We're going to the office in Seoul
我们要去首尔的办公室一趟
what
什么
what happened?
发生了什么事吗
Something happened in the office
办公室里出了点事
Let’s have dinner together next time
下次再一起吃饭吧
it's me
是我
Something seems to have happened in Dingchen's office
定辰的办公室好像出事了
Oh my god
天啊
What? What's going on? aunt
什么啊 这是怎么回事 阿姨
Boss, let’s call the police first
老板 我们先报警吧
Dingchen has no enemies and no debts
定辰没有仇家 也没有欠债
don't you know anything
你什么都不知道吗
What's going on
到底是怎么回事
You are so noisy
你好吵
Stop talking first, stinky girl
你先别说话 臭丫头
Boss Jin
金老板
I was worried so I followed.
我很担心所以就跟来了
What the hell is going on
这到底是怎么回事
I heard that a group of unknown guys broke in.
听说有群身分不明的家伙闯进来
The person in charge of our branch was kidnapped
绑走了我们分公司的负责人
Do you have any suspects?
你们有怀疑对象吗
Someone will call
会有人打来的
Hello
喂
car boss
车老板
I am Lao Bian from Xingxingye
我是明星兴业的老卞
I just got a call
我刚才接到了一通电话
I heard my boys got into trouble
听说我的小弟们闯了祸
They said they were going to lose their jobs
他们说他们要丢掉饭碗了
Reluctant to let Miss Wu go
不肯放过吴小姐
So that's it
原来如此
In fact, I already guessed it was you
其实我早就猜到是你了
I knew it was him
就知道是他
But…
不过…
Boss Bian, I thought you were an entrepreneur
卞老板我以为你是企业家
I didn’t expect you to be a gangster.
没想到你是个流氓啊
If you're a man, don't mince words. Speak directly if you have anything to say
是男子汉就别拐弯抹角 有话直说
What do you want?
你到底想怎么样
It’s great that the boss of the car is so direct in his speech.
车老板讲话就是这么直接 真好
ok
好吧
Take the theater I was originally responsible for
把我原本负责的戏院
Give it back to me
还给我
Remove your people
撤走你的人
what
什么
What nonsense are you talking about?
你在说什么鬼话
Really
真是
Hey, catch her
喂 把她抓好
car boss
车老板
I'm not kidding
我没在开玩笑
I, the younger brothers, have never read any books.
我这些小弟没念过什么书
Not polite
不懂礼貌
I finally stopped them
我好不容易才阻止了他们
They said they would only give two days
他们说只给两天的时间
You don’t want to take the Jingjiang District Theater Letter of termination comes
你不拿和京江地区戏院的 解约书来
I may never see Miss Wu again
可能会再也见不到吴小姐
That's a really good idea
那真是个好主意
You helped me solve a problem
你帮我解决了一个麻烦
Just do whatever you want
你想怎么样就怎么样吧
I do like Miss Wu very much
我确实很喜欢吴小姐
But I'm also a little afraid of her
但我也有点怕她
To put it harshly, she is my right-hand man But not my daughter
说难听点 她虽然是我的左右手 但可不是我的女儿
I will also worry that she will betray me in the future So a little uneasy
我也会担心她将来会背叛我 所以有点不安
This is just right
这样刚好
I mean it, Boss Bian
我是说真的 卞老板
i won't tell anyone
我不会告诉任何人
Please help me get rid of her
你帮我把她处理掉吧
Throw her into the iron barrel
把她扔进铁桶里
Take it to the reservoir and throw it away
载去蓄水池丢吧
Thank you for your hard work
那辛苦你了
Hello…
喂…
car boss
车老板
Hello Che Jinyu
喂 车锦玉
This crazy woman
这疯婆子
you're dead
你死定了
Don't stand in the way
别挡在这
Miss Wu
吴小姐
Your boss…
你老板…
Want me to kill you
要我杀了你
are you crazy
你疯了吗
what
什么
you're dead
你死定了
Shit Boss
大便老板
Shit…
大便…
you woman
你这女人
I'm going crazy
我要疯了
Hello
喂
Put here…
把这里…
tidy up
收拾一下
put her...
把她…
get rid of her
把她处理掉
Come on...get rid of her quickly
快点…快把她处理掉
you guy
你这家伙
Crazy woman, you are looking for death
疯婆子 你找死啊
aunt
阿姨
You want to kill Dingchen?
你想害死定辰啊
Whether she can live or not is her life.
能不能活是她的命
There are still people who will not die so easily
还有人不会那么容易死
I'll call the police now
我现在就报警
aunt
阿姨
If we lose momentum now, everyone will die together.
现在输了气势 大家就得一起死
People who need help will come to their door.
有求于人的人会自己上门
Wait a minute
等等吧
Dingchen was kidnapped
定辰被绑架了
what to do now
现在该怎么办
I don’t know when Yongbi will come to see you You can't ask the younger brothers to look for them separately.
不知道永弼什么时候会来找你 不能叫小弟们分头去找
too dangerous
太危险了
We don't know each other either What kind of organization is it?
我们也不知道对方 是怎么样的组织
Call all the boys immediately
立刻叫所有小弟
Find where Dingchen is
去找定辰在哪
Douxue
斗学
don't worry
别担心
50 million for foreign wine and 30 million for beer.
洋酒五千万 啤酒三千万
A total of 80 million won was washed
一共洗了八千万韩元
what is the method
方法是什么
I charge normal drink prices
我收正常的酒钱
Give him the rest in cash and help him launder money.
剩下的还他现金 帮他洗钱
But you want to teach him a lesson
不过你是想教训他
Still want to kill him
还是想杀了他
kill him
杀了他
To track Douxue’s whereabouts
去追踪斗学的行踪
Call everyone to assemble
叫大家集合
Yes eldest brother
是 大哥
(Xingxingye is on vacation)
(明星兴业休假中)
Boss Bian’s whereabouts cannot be found
查不到卞老板的行踪
Ji Su asked them to keep looking.
吉洙那边 叫他们继续找
Xuanyu, please ask them to come back.
宣宇那边 叫他们回来吧
No need to do that
不用那样
Hey brat
喂 臭小子
What if Yong Pil comes looking for you now?
如果永弼现在来找你怎么办
Do you think he will let you go?
你觉得他会放过你吗
Mom…
妈…
What's wrong
怎么了
The urinal is full
尿壶满了
Wait
等等
what is this doing
这是在做什么
This is not a prison
这里又不是监狱
Where's dad?
爸呢
Don't know
不知道
He went out to smoke after dinner
他吃完晚餐出去抽烟了
Give me the urinal
尿壶给我
what are you doing
你干嘛
Hey stinky girl
喂 臭丫头
Don't stop yet
还不给我站住
Hello
喂
Yes aunt
是 阿姨
what
什么
Your sister ran away from your mother's house
你妹从你妈家逃走了
Why is everything going wrong today?
今天怎么诸事不顺
are you sure
你确定吗
Are there only four of them?
他们只有四个人吗
Yes, there are only four of them
对 他们只有四个人
No... there are only three people
不对… 只有三个人
Got it
知道了
Tell everyone to copy the guy and get ready to go out
叫大家抄家伙 准备出动
Call Mr. Park
打电话给朴常务
Yes eldest brother
是 大哥
Brat, you're dead
臭小子 你死定了
(Waterfall Nightclub)
(瀑布夜总会)
scared me
吓我一跳
Didn't Zhenyu come to find you?
贞玉没来找你吗
I haven't seen her since that day
那天之后我就没见过她了
If she comes to you
她如果来找你
Give her this money, saying it's car money
给她这些钱 说是车钱
I'll help you get it to her
我会帮你拿给她
But I'm not a night school person Not from the union either.
但我既不是夜校的人 也不是工会的人
Will she come to me?
她会来找我吗
If she is caught by the police again
她如果再被警察抓到
No one can help her
谁也帮不了她
Help me tell her to go back to her hometown in the south of the city quickly.
你帮我叫她快点回城南老家
Please, Ms. Yoshiko
拜托你了 吉子小姐
What's going on
什么情况
On…
上…
Who is this
这是哪位
Turns out it’s my brother Douxue
原来是我的兄弟斗学啊
I almost had a car accident. I'm still wondering who it was.
差点出车祸 我还在想是谁
Have you eaten?
你吃饭没
We're going to a dinner party. Do you want to come with us?
我们要去聚餐 你要一起去吗
drive away
把车开走
If you are caught by the police, you will be ticketed.
被警察抓到会被开罚单
Issue a ticket
开罚单
If you are fired, you will be fired
被开就被开
As long as it allows you to...
只要能让你…
Get out of our gang
滚出我们帮派
If brother knew
大哥如果知道
you may suffer
你可能会遭殃
No
不
He will find it interesting
他会觉得很有趣
You're doing this because I won't let you in the hotel Is this how you eat soup and rice?
你是因为我不让你在饭店里 吃汤饭才这样吗
sorry
对不起
But…
但是…
If you want to eat soup and rice, go to the soup rice restaurant. You little hooligan
要吃汤饭就去汤饭餐厅吃 你这小流氓
Brat
臭小子
Just now
就是现在
what are you doing
你们在做什么
"Where did it all go wrong?"
"从哪里开始出错的"
"I don't know"
"我不知道"
"It's useless to talk too much anyway"
"反正多说无益"
"It's all in the past"
"都是过去的事了"
"Cannot hide"
"无法隐藏"
"Missing you"
"对你的思念"
"It broke out"
"就此爆发"
"Can I come back to you again?"
"我能再回到你身边吗"
"Can't hide the uneasy look"
"掩饰不住不安的眼神"
"Those Bygone Days"
"过往的那些日子"
"your name"
"你的名字"
"It's deeply etched in my heart"
"深深刻在我心上"
help him up
扶他起来
You say I'm a hooligan
你说我是小流氓啊
Really?
是吗
You are so powerful but you defeated me today
你这么厉害 今天却打输我啦
after you go to hell
你下地狱后
It's better not to meet the hooligans again
最好不要再遇到小流氓
What are you doing?
搞什么
Are you crazy?
你这小子疯了吗
Hey, take him to the hospital quickly
喂 快带他去医院
Come
来
Come here you idiot
过来 你这蠢蛋
I came too late
我太晚来了
Don’t you like excitement?
你不是喜欢刺激的吗
Douxue
斗学
It would be the end if we were raided
我们如果被突袭就完了
We should ask Xuan Yu's people to withdraw.
应该叫宣宇那边的人撤回来
Hello Li Douxue
喂 李斗学
Brother
哥
Change your strategy
换个策略吧
I'll deal with Yong Pil
我去应付永弼
what
什么
you alone
你一个人
You want to die so much
你那么想死啊
I will take two people with me now
我现在就带两个人
Go to where Zhenyu lives
去贞玉住的地方
Yongbi should have sent someone to follow me.
永弼应该有派人在跟踪我
What better opportunity than this?
哪有比这更好的机会
Anyway, I don’t know when I will be raided.
反正不知道何时会被突袭
Just seduce him first
干脆先引诱他
I'm going to find Brother Guangzhuo
我去找光卓哥
That's right
没错
This method is much better than a head-on battle
比起正面决战 这方法好多了
This way our people won't get hurt
这样我们的人可以不用受伤
It also stimulated Brother Guang Zhuo's compassion.
还能刺激了光卓哥的怜悯心
What if something happens to you?
万一你出了什么事呢
Of course it's your fault if you come too late
你太晚来的话当然是你的错
madman
疯子
Does it have to go to this point?
一定要做到这种地步吗
How can it be exciting enough if you don’t work hard?
不拚命怎么够刺激
Is there any news about the person who went to Dingchen?
去找定辰的人没有消息吗
Not at all
完全没有
Who is she to you?
她对你来说到底是什么人
Why do you do so much for her
你为什么要为她做这么多
Invest in film company shares
投资电影公司股分
and ownership of the Nanhai Theater
还有南海戏院的所有权
You work so hard just to find her Isn't it?
你会这么拚命都是为了找她 不是吗
I don't know either
我也不知道
Maybe it’s because I feel empty
可能是觉得空虚吧
What's going on?
发什么神经
I feel empty just like Yong Pil Go to eat soup rice
觉得空虚就跟永弼一样 去吃汤饭
Really? It turns out he feels empty too
是吗 原来他也觉得空虚啊
Really
真是的
is this true
这是真的吗
How dare I lie to brother
我怎么敢对大哥说谎
I'm not saying this out of selfishness
我不是因为私心才这么说的
I swear, bro
我发誓 大哥
You just because he embezzled some public funds Do you just want to kill him?
你只因为他盗用了一点公款 就想杀他吗
Not like that
不是那样的
I heard that he wanted to expand his power kill you
我听说他想在壮大自己的势力后 杀了您
He uses your money to please his younger brothers.
他拿您的钱去讨好小弟们
You also know
您也知道吧
Recently, everyone listens to him more
最近大家更听他的话
And I just wanted to hurt his leg
还有我本来只是想伤他一条腿
Douxue this guy
斗学这家伙
Duplicitous guy
表里不一的家伙
Big brother
大哥
(money cashier book)
(金钱出纳簿)
I have never heard of Guan Yu and Zhang Fei
我可没听说过关羽和张飞
Will cheat Liu Bei's money And stabbed him in the back
会骗刘备的钱 还从背后捅了他一刀
Is this considered a sworn friendship in Taoyuan?
这也算桃园结义吗
I've never heard of Liu Bei doubting his younger brother.
我也没听说过刘备会怀疑弟弟
This account book is fake
这本帐簿是假的
I can bet my life
我能赌上我的命
Hey, you guys also bet together
喂 你们也一起赌
Brat, you're looking for death
臭小子 你找死啊
I have witnesses
我有证人
Hello, Executive Park
喂 朴常务
Did you say you laundered the money for me?
你说你帮我洗了钱吗
Brother, it’s all over
大哥 已经都结束了
Just admit it
你就承认吧
Brother
哥
come in
进来吧
long time no see
好久不见
What?
什么啊
Have they worked with you?
他们和您共事过吧
They are the Republic of Korea
他们是大韩民国
The most powerful forger
最厉害的伪造达人
Hello Yongbi
喂 永弼
You know them too, right?
你也认识他们吧
What do you want us to help look at?
你要我们帮忙看什么
This is the alcohol trading account book for the past two years
这是这两年的酒类交易帐簿
They said this would prove me Misappropriated 80 million public funds
他们说这个可以证明我 挪用了八千万公款
You guys check it out
你们检查看看
Eighty million?
八千万吗
You stole money
你偷钱啊
Don't steal money
别偷钱
You have to teach him a lesson before he can cheer up.
要教训他一顿 他才会打起精神
But if someone wants to frame him
但如果是有人想栽赃他
Then you have to give that person a good beating.
那也得揍那个人一顿
Replace eyes, nose and mouth with eyes
用眼睛换眼鼻嘴
Trade hands with teeth
用牙齿换手
The rules in this circle It's quite strict to begin with
这个圈子里的规定 本来就比较严格
Hey, how dare you come here?
喂 你们怎么敢来这里
Get out of here
快滚
I'm so scared
我好怕
How is it
怎么样
are we going out
我们要出去吗
No, you decide
不 你们判断一下
Brother, this is our family’s problem
大哥 这是我们自家人的问题
They are my family too
他们也是我的家人
You guys keep talking
你们继续说
Feng Hao, look carefully
风浩 你看仔细一点
good
好
Check to see
确认看看
look at this
看看这个
too rough
太粗糙了
Paper is different from old to new The color is much different
纸的新旧还不一样 颜色差很多
And these numbers were scratched with a knife
还有这些数字用刀刮过
I'm not an amateur. How do I do this?
又不是业余的人 怎么这样做事
So this kind of work
所以这种工作
Should be left to professionals like me
应该交给我这种专业人士
What are you talking about? Impossible
你在胡说什么 不可能
Hey, come here and talk more carefully
喂 你过来说仔细一点
I committed a capital crime, President
我犯了死罪 会长
It was Brother Yongbi who ordered me...
是永弼哥指使我…
Don't talk nonsense
你不要胡说八道
Brother, wait a minute
大哥 等等
a leg
一条腿
Do you still want to cripple a person’s leg?
你还想废人一条腿啊
That's why you...
所以你才会…
Being called a hooligan
被人说是小流氓
Useless trash
没用的废物
From now on you...
你以后…
Dare to appear in front of me again
敢再出现在我面前
He's dead
就死定了
Did you hear that?
听到没
take him out
把他带出去
So
所以啊
Don't worry if anyone is looking for you
有没有人找 你别管
This is what you have to do in business
做生意本来就得做这种事
You woman talk too much
你这女人话还真多
I'm going to die
我要挂了
Really
真是的
Brother, the time is coming
大哥 时间快到了
She thinks I can't do it
她觉得我下不了手啊
Then come and give it a try
那就来试试看
Who do you think I am?
把我当什么人了
Thank you, brothers
谢谢各位大哥
And eldest sister
还有大姊
what are you talking about
你在说什么
you are our boss
你是我们的老大
Something happened to the boss
老大出事
How can we survive?
我们哪活得了
Yeah, but you almost got into trouble
是啊 不过你差点就出大事了
Yes
是啊
That account book is guaranteed to be genuine
那帐簿做得如假包换
They probably found someone better than me.
他们大概是找了比我更厉害的人
I've read that account book
我看完那本帐簿
My whole back is sweating
整个背都在冒冷汗
Fortunately, Executive Park admitted that he felt guilty.
还好朴常务自己心虚承认了
Otherwise you might almost get into trouble
不然你差点就要出事了
I was so worried that my heart almost stopped.
我刚才担心得心跳都快停了
Thought I would die
还以为我会死掉
We act with you because we believe you
我们是相信你才陪你演戏
Otherwise…
不然…
We almost ended up together
我们差点就要一起完蛋了
Dou Xue
斗学啊
We all have only one life
我们都只有一条命
Don't take too many risks
你不要太冒险
Didn't you also say
你不是也说过
Don't want to see anything happen to us
不想看我们出事
sorry
对不起
I'm too impatient
我太心急了
Okay, it's okay
好了 没事
Then let's not disturb the boss.
那我们不要打扰老大了
let's go back
我们回去吧
we are a family
我们是一家人
family
一家人
Let's go
我们走罗
Be careful
你小心点
good we will always be a family
好 我们永远是一家人
Sorry, brother
对不起 大哥
I have sent all my brothers
我已经派所有兄弟
I searched all the organizations in Seoul.
找遍首尔所有的组织了
But I can't find out
但打听不到
It seems they are from other counties and cities.
看来是其他县市来的
It's not a nationwide case
又不是全国性的案子
Now our strength alone is not enough
现在光靠我们的力量不够
I asked a detective I know to check it out.
我拜托认识的刑警查了一下
That boss Bian has no criminal record
那位卞老板没有任何前科
This kind of person absconded
这种人潜逃了
Time is not on our side, right?
时间不是站在我们这边的吧
If he decides to hide
他如果下定决心躲起来
Even the police and prosecutors
就算是警察 检察官
It's impossible to find him right away
也不可能马上找到他
right
对吧
But…
不过…
I watch movies
我看电影
A place like the CIA in the United States
像美国CIA那种地方
You can find it in just a few dozen minutes
几十分钟马上就能找到
That's a movie
那是电影
That's a made-up story
那是编造的故事
made up story
编造的故事
Hello Xuanyu Yes
喂 宣宇 是
Go and drive
去开车
where are you going
你要去哪里
Since it is beyond our capabilities
既然力不从心
Just go find someone for help.
就去找人帮忙吧
Why are you telling me now?
你为什么现在才跟我说
no time
没时间了
Just tell me if I can find it
你告诉我能不能找到就好
Brother, I'm not a prosecutor yet
哥 我还不是检察官
You should go to the police...
你应该去报警…
You should go to the police first
你应该先去报警
Must find her
一定要找到她
no time
没时间了
But…
不过…
Aren’t you no longer nostalgic for Dingchen?
你不是对定辰没有留恋了
Are you still paying attention to her latest news?
还一直在关心她的动态吗
That's because...
那是因为…
I have a business relationship with her boss
我跟她老板有生意上的关系
I knew that by accident
那也是偶然知道的
If you are willing to help
你如果愿意帮忙
There should be a way
应该会有办法
what does it mean
什么意思
The Security and Enterprise Department wanted to use you as a mole before.
之前想利用你当内鬼的安企部
How could you say such things to me?
你怎么能跟我说这种话
you don't know those guys Did it cause any trauma to me?
你不知道那些家伙 对我造成了什么创伤吗
you owe me a debt
你欠我的债
I will treat you as half of what you paid me back
我会当你还了我一半
you must help
你一定要帮忙
This is the only way now
现在只有这个办法
(Oasis)
(绿洲Oasis)
Is Choi Cheol-woong Choi Young-sik’s biological flesh and blood?
崔哲雄是崔英植的亲生骨肉吗
what does this mean
这是什么意思
I want to go out independently
我要独立出去
I knew this girl would betray me
我就知道这丫头一定会背叛我
Stop making such jokes
你不要再开这种玩笑了
No, I want to keep driving
不要 我要继续开
I want to continue to compete with you
我要继续跟你竞争
Make Dingchen my woman
把定辰变成我的女人
He is a murderer...
他是杀人犯耶…
Hey, I'm not dating a murderer.
喂 我不是在跟杀人犯交往
Do you think I'm pitiful?
你觉得我很可怜吗
Hello…
喂…
Leave everything behind and come to me
你抛下一切 来我这里吧
I will stay with you
我会陪在你身边